[{"answer": "I guess play piano, you know, because that's the thing I started doing when I was a little kid.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "If I cut off your cord to everything else and left you with one thing, what would you do?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "No, I was playing \"When the Saints Go Marching In\" at the age of 5.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "You were playing Mozart at the age of 5, right?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "Well, my dad was the district attorney of New Orleans for about 30 years.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "When was the moment you thought, this could be more than just a hobby, this could be -- this could be my lifetime thing?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "No, you really can't.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "You can't buy it, can you?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "If somebody older than you walked in the room, you should stand up?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "Right?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "She had cancer?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "I knew she was not feeling well.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "Did you realize that she was dying or not?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "He still lives there and he's in great health and he's handsome and strong and got an incredible moral and ethical backbone.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "He still lives in New Orleans?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "Oh my gosh, man.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "What would she have made of what's happened to you, your mom did?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "I heard about it on -- I knew the storm was coming.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "When did you hear about it and how quickly did you realize how bad it was?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "It's hard to articulate, Piers.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "And when you got there and saw the scale of devastation -- I mean, as someone who had been born there, raised there, what was going through your mind?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "Well, I'm not privy to all of the details that unfolded and led people to make certain decisions.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "Why was it not just obvious there was this awful disaster unfurling?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "Some people, you know, said it was kind of surreptitious racism, that it was the fact that there were so many poor black people meant that the authorities didn't respond in the way, if they had all been middle class white people.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "I -- you know, at this point, what good is it going to do to blame local or state or federal government?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "Awesome.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "And what is New Orleans like these days?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "You know, we never really talked about it.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Was he scathing of the authorities?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "-- underneath this gentle cheery exterior.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "Are you sure about that?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "I don't know if I want to think about that.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "How many people do you think have made love to your music over the years, Harry?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "When I thought you couldn't get any more sickening in terms of the perfect life and career, I remembered that you actually married a Victoria's Secret model.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "Because when she makes me put out the trash, seduction isn't part of that order, you know?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "How did you wangle that?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "Oh, is that right?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "-- throw themselves at you?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "Doing movies.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "When you say been with, what do you mean, Harry?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "ORGAN: I wasn't quite sure if I was losing a bit of --", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "You talking about another way?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "I did, on a few occasions.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "Did you ever meet Frank Sinatra?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "ONNICK: Oh, I don't think he thought of me like that.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "What does he think of you as the young upstart?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "I mean, this guy had 40, 50 years of people saying that they were upstarts.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "No?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "The closest thing to advice that he gave me was when I asked him how he hit this high A flat -- we did have a similar range.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "Did he give you any advice?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "I mean, it's not great advice, because you need to be Frank Sinatra for it to work, right?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "I don't -- I wouldn't say that was what made him great.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "Is that -- was that a technical thing that he had over other people?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "I still can't hit that note.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "And that one piece of advice he gave you, have you been able to do it?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "-- at the Beverly Hilton in LA.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "Were you there?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "I was --", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "Do you -- do you remember that?", "qSentId": 587}, {"answer": "You were terrible.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "Do you remember how bad I was?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "He didn't even look at me.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "He didn't even reply to you?", "qSentId": 621}, {"answer": "I like to watch sort of from afar and learn what I can, just as a citizen.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 647, "question": "But, I mean generally, do -- do you get fired up politics, by what's going on to your country?", "qSentId": 646}, {"answer": "I do enjoy --", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 662, "question": "-- do you watch the debates?", "qSentId": 661}, {"answer": "I think, you know, right now it's -- it's interesting to -- to see what everyone has to say and what --", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 667, "question": "Are you -- do you -- do you veer to either party or no?", "qSentId": 666}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 671, "question": "Out of the Republicans?", "qSentId": 670}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 682, "question": "Did you vote Obama last time?", "qSentId": 681}, {"answer": "Yes, he really can.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 720, "question": "Can he sing?", "qSentId": 719}, {"answer": "I'd like to do it.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 742, "question": "Are you going to do it?", "qSentId": 741}, {"answer": "Previews start November the 12th.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 770, "question": "When is it launching?", "qSentId": 769}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 775, "question": "And I'm assuming there will be some hot tickets for me here, Harry, right?", "qSentId": 774}, {"answer": "Standing room only.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 782, "question": "What's that?", "qSentId": 781}, {"answer": "I think you should sing to me, because it will look more awkward.", "docId": "111216pmt", "aSentId": 795, "question": "-- to America?", "qSentId": 794}]